One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Until I can reach the sky,
I believe, until the next tomorrow, hey
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring.
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style.
It begins, it expands, this flavor that exceeds imagination
I feel so good throughout my body, I will become free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far.
Share the one dream, by telling each other.
Share the good times and laugh.
I'll keep going until I can reach the sky.
Let's overcome it now, I believe in the next tomorrow yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall.
I'll be there soon, I believe in one world yeah yeah...
Navy HQ
The Dark King, Silvers Rayleigh, huh?
It would appear the others haven't noticed, and think he's just a normal old guy.
They're gonna sell the Dark King in the Human Auction, huh?
The Auction House Incident
If he's the real deal, then this is a really bad situation...
Although my subordinates can't be 100% sure...
Tea!
Uh, right.
What should we do, vice-admiral? Should I report this to Fleet Admiral Sengoku?
Nah, I'll handle this myself. Don't tell anyone else, not even Sengoku!
Make sure to tell your subordinates!
But if it really is him...
It's him. No doubt about that.
I hear some reports about the guy from time to time.
I'd say he's probably ended up losing his freedom in a gamble.
He might be an old man, but if we try to take on Rayleigh unprepared,
I'd say we'd probably lose countless soldiers in the attempt.
It's especially dangerous right now.
You think the Navy can handle two legends at the same time?!
Grove 1
Human Auction Site
Well then, everyone! Thank you for your patience!
In a moment, the 1st grove's monthly tradition...
the Great Human Auction, shall commence!
Our host, of course, is this man!
The walking super bazaar...
Mr. Disco!
Good day, everyone! This time, we've got quite an excellent selection of slaves for you!
You are all lucky! We've got a spectacular deluxe item for later in the show!
The only thing on my mind is making sure everyone here leaves with the slave they've been waiting for!
Well, then, let us start the auction!
Prepare numbers 2 and 3.
Understood!
Entry #1: from Toroa in West Blue!
A master of instruments from a musician family!
A pirate standing proud and tall!
With his instrument, he'll play any music you want,
a human music box!
Give him a mop, and he will clean up any filth perfectly!
He is also a fantastic wine maker!
A 25 year old human male, a perfect working age!
192 cm, 130 kg, name: Byron!
We will start off the bidding with the special starting price of 480 thousand belly!
Well, then, raise your plate if you wish to place a bid!
Number 82 makes a bid of 500 thousand belly!
We have 600 thousand from number 7! Anyone else?!
Sold, for 600 thousand belly!
Note: Human trade
What's this, Duval?
This disgusting list?
It's the market prices.
Market prices?
Basic auction minimum prices...
Humans, 500 thousand belly.
Male giants are 50 million belly...
What? Female mermen are sold for 70 million belly?!
You understand why everyone tries to catch mermaids now, right?
The value is something else!
You can do whatever you want to them once you've bought them...
but they usually end up in some rich person's aquarium.
They have to live out their lives as decorations in small tanks.
What're you trying to say, damn you?!
Now that I think about it though, you can hardly call that "living" at all.
If that's what you think, then hurry up and find her!
We've covered all the slave-traders stationed in the 20's!
Hurry up and go into the air!
Don't make it sound so easy!
This ain't a bird, you know, it's gotta pick up speed first!
Camie! Where are you?!
This is what's getting to me!
Kidnapping team "Coffee Monkeys"
It was a giant, damn it! It was easy enough to catch the guy sleeping...
but do you have any idea how hard it was to carry'im?!
Of course, you'd think we'd gotten the big draw this time, right?
That's how it usually is, right?
But then some guy went and brought a freakin' mermaid to the auction house!
Who wouldn't get drunk when somethin' like that happens?
Hang on! Who was that?
This is unit 5, to all Rosy Life Riders!
Can you hear me? The guy who took the mermaid is Peterman!
The place they took her to was the auction in Grove 1!
Did you say it was Peterman?
Did you find it out?
Yeah, let's fly!
This is a little too fast! I am scared!
She hasn't been sold already, has she?
Hurry!
Grove 1 should be nearby! Leave it to me!
We'll head towards the Auction House!
You figured out where she is? Thank god!
Camie!
Hurry!
I'd like to return to the ship, but where's the number 1 tree?
I'll tell you!
Well, well, let us keep going! Here is entry #6!
A 10-pack of male human workers!
This is the Head, calling all men! Get me some info on today's auction!
It started at 4 o'clock, and it's been going for 30 minutes already!
Hey, will this really be alright?
No problem at all!
A mermaid would certainly be the main event, so they'll save her for the end!
We'll make it!
Anyway, take the fastest route! This thing is slower than the Flying Fish!
Like I said, calm down, Master Black Leg!
I'm the Head of this team! Did you see me change my course after we learned the mermaid's location?
Uh, no...
That's because...
I've been heading to Grove 1 from the beginning!
Look ahead! That's Grove 1! I am the Head, so I got here before everyone else!
Are you serious?
This must be the intuition of a professional!
We've arrived, Reindeer-san!
Thank you. Huh?
Oh, Sanji!
You lost, didn't you?!
Be careful!
Yeah! Thanks a lot!
What's with this guy?
200 thousand belly! Anyone else?
Sold!
Is this it?
Like I said, why can't you give her back?!
I'm telling you that Camie-chan is not for sale!
You're the one who's out of line here!
If you don't drop it soon, I can take legal countermeasures!
You're disturbing our business!
Those guys...!
What do you mean, "business", you damn bastard?!
Do you think I'll accept a business like this in this world?!
A lawless pirate like yourself has no right to lecture me about morality!
Slave-trading is a worldwide taboo! How much did you pay the government?
What an ill-mannered accusation...
But I suppose you're right!
When talking to the government or marines,
it seems that terms like "slave-trading" are hard for them comprehend.
It's as if they have no idea that this business of ours exists!
How ridiculous... So the whole system is crooked, then?!
How can the government tolerate this?!
So, could you please...
This is annoying!
We're sure the mermaid is in there, so let's just break her out!
Weapons...
No! There are Celestial Dragons inside!
And if Camie has been brought here, then she's probably got a neck ring already!
That exploding thing?!
Then, we can't just get her out?
If you'd please leave then.
Why, you...!
No, Sanji!
Let me go, Chopper!
I can't, Sanji!
Damn it...
If the guy won't listen, then...!
Hey, Girlie! Where are you going?
I said calm down, Sanji!
If we can't hurt them, then we'll just play by their rules to get Camie back!
Backstage
Bring out numbers 15 and 16.
Understood.
Please stop!
I don't want to! I'd rather stay in the cell!
I don't wanna be a slave!
Help me, please! Help!
Give him a tranquilizer.
Call the Navy! Please!
Don't sell me, please!
Hacchin... Save me!
Noooooo!
Chief, I think that's the Straw Hat crew.
The Straw Hats' captain isn't there...
I was hoping to see just how dumb he was myself...
Now, things are heating up, on this Grand Human Auction!
Our next entry is an instant purchase, for sure!
Entry number 15 is a knockout female slave!
Please observe the miraculous proportions of this 20 year old dancer, Pascia!
She's one of today's big draws!
Her marvelous dancing figure is sure to impress even the heavens!
We've got loads of treasure stored on the ship.
It's at least 200 million in all...
What's the going price for a mermaid?
If you have that much, then it should be enough, but I can't repay that!
What, Hachi? Are you Camie's guardian or something?
It's not like that...
If it's to get our friend back, then I don't care how much we have to pay!
Everyone agrees, right?
Of course! This isn't about money!
Thanks a lot... you guys...
I'll never forget this...!
That's the Nami-san I love!
Shut up and come on.
Hurry! Hurry!
I get it!
Hurry to Grove 1!
So this is Grove 2, huh?
Then it's the next one, right?
Is everyone there yet?
Extra! Extra!
Is the World Government out of its mind?
If they really do this, then...!
Captain, this could mean trouble!
Is that how it is?
Is something wrong, Captain Drake?
I understand now...
Seeing how close this island is to Navy HQ...
I thought it was strange that there were so few marines around.
What has happened?
It's been decided that Fire Fist Ace, commander of Whitebeard's second division, is set to be executed!
If they do that, then Whitebeard is sure to make a move!
There's gonna be a war!
Entry #15!
The beautiful dancer, Pascia!
With a splendid starting bid of 800 thousand belly,
the bid has risen to an amazing 7 million 200 thousand belly!
Ah... We have finally arrived.
Well well, things are heating up now...
What will be the next item up for bid?!
Good, the auction is still going.
However they're almost done.
This one is truly useless!
Hey! Have this one sold off too! I don't want him anymore.
I'll do the paperwork right away.
A Celestial Dragon...
Another one showed up... One of the World Nobles...
Those guys that can call an admiral from the Navy if we attack them, huh?
I would like a mermaid... Are they gonna sell one today?
It seems that mermaids are quite difficult to catch...
so I doubt they've got one this time.
Oh, my! Saint Charlos!
Hurry and take me to my seat!
Yes, right away, Sir!
So, you are finally here, big brother Charlos?
Well then, it seems we're ready...
Entry #16 is...
Can you believe it?! A pirate captain!
A wanted man with a bounty of 17 million belly! His name is Lacuba!
He is a pirate famous for his delicate, intricate planning! His well built body is also worthy of note.
He'd make an excellent transport, hard worker, or sandbag!
A practical choice if I ever saw one!
Now then...!
Don't tell me, he...?!
He collapsed! What's going on?!
I saw blood!
Hey! Hurry up and pull the curtains!
What just happened?
He bit his tongue.
He decided that he didn't want to live his life as a slave...
and figured it would be better to just die right now.
I suppose that's actually a logical choice.
Aren't they going to bring out the mermaid soon?
I'm sure Camie is really scared...
Just hang in there a little longer...
We're going to save you!
Fortunately, we have the treasure from Thriller Bark!
Thanks a lot, you guys...
This is no good...
God damn it! We can't sell him now... That idiot!
The mermaid is up next, right?
Yes. We're ready to get her whenever you want us to.
Alright!
Get her out, now!
Yes!
Well then, about #16!
It would appear that the pirate Lacuba got a little nervous... He had a nosebleed, and collapsed.
We'll put him up for sale again later.
However, everyone...!
The next item we're going to bring out now...
is a super deluxe-item that's sure to make you forget all about this trouble!
Countless people have tried to capture one...
Please look at this silhouette!
Could it be...?!
An introduction should not be necessary... Just have a look with your own eyes!
Thank you for your patience! Well then, here it comes!
Have a good look at this!
Straight from Fishman Island...
Camie, the mermaid!!!
It's real! A young mermaid!
Hacchin and the others! They're here to save me!
Camie! They've brought out Camie!
Alright, we're gonna take her back!
We've got 200 million after all!
Camie!
Finally! A mermaid! They're selling a mermaid!
Five hundred million!!
I'll buy it for 500 million belly!
No use... We can't beat that...
What's that? We don't have that much!
You've gone and wasted our money again.
You already have piranhas in your fish tank, do you not?
I'd like too see them try and chase after her...
Mermaids are the fastest sea-creatures in the world.
I can't hear the voices outside...
Get me out of here, Hacchin!
It would appear that the audience has been rendered speechless...
Well, does anyone want to make a higher bid than 500 million?
There's gotta be something we can do...
Hey, Sanji?
Nami?
This can't be happening! They can't take our friend away just because we don't have enough money!
This is bad... We never considered this possibility...
If we can't get her back with money, then the situation has gotten even worse!
If not, then this auction will be quite a short one!
Now that it's come to this, I might as well just take her back by force and run off to the sea!
Don't be ridiculous! What about the neck-ring?
You'd just blow her up!
Then I just have to get the key to that ring somehow...
That's enough time!
I did it!
It's like a symbol of how messed up the world is...
I've seen enough of this farce. We're leaving.
Well then, thank you for your attention up until now.
The main prize this time, the mermaid Camie...
goes to the World Noble, Saint Charlos for the price of 500 million belly...
It's...
What?!
...a deal!
How noisy.
Luffy!
What the heck?! Couldn't you land any better than that?!
No way! It's a Flying Fish, you know!
And it was you who told me to crash into the building!
Anyway, you told me to get on...
But why were you in such a hurry to get back to the Sunny anyway?
Where are we?
Zoro, too?
You guys!
Hey, that's Straw Hat Luffy!
What's with those guys? Who are they?
Oh! Camie!
Luffy-chin!
Camie! I looked for you!
Thank God!
Wait a second, Straw Hat! What are you doing?
What do you mean?! Camie's right there!
She's there, but she's got an exploding neck-ring attached! So you can't just take her!
Besides, the Celestial Dragons are here!
Like I care!
He's a pirate!
Camie!
Just stop already!
A fishman!
That's disgusting!
What's a fishman doing here?
You octopus monster!
I'm gonna save you right now, Camie!
Get him!
Damn you! Camie isn't for sale!
Don't let him get any closer to the stage!
What's a fishman doing on land?
No, don't get any closer! It's creepy!
Hey, staff! Hurry up and restrain him!
No, don't come here!
Go back to the sea, you monster!
Yeah, that's right!
Get off this island!
Get lost!
Hachi! Hurry up and escape!
You're the one who's in trouble now!
I'm fine! What about Camie?
What's going on here?
It's just like Robin said...
Mermen and fishmen are discriminated against on this island!
Discriminated against...?
Even Camie and Hachi?!
I hit it! I shot a fishman!
Hachi!
I'm glad he shot it!
I was afraid that if it came any closer, we might get infected by it!
He was definitely trying to cause some trouble... After all, they've only got the brains of a fish!
Father, please look! I caught a fishman!
I caught it myself, so it's for free!
Free! Free! An octopus for free!
I got it, I got it!
An octopus-slave for free! Free!
W... Wait... Please...
Straw Hat...
You can't... get upset...
I was just careless, that's all...
You promised that... even if someone was shot right before your eyes...
you wouldn't lay a hand on the Celestial Dragons, right?!
After all, I used to be a pirate...
I did so many awful things, so...
I had this coming...
Sorry...
I never wanted this to happen...
I just wanted... to make up for all the things I did to Nami...!
I was trying to help you, but...
As always...
I just screw up no matter what I do...!
I really am... clumsy after all...
Hachi...
In the end... I just caused you trouble...!
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
Damn fish!
Even after I shot you, you keep on blabbering! You're annoying!
You, what's with that look of yours?!
Stop it, Straw!
If you do that, you'll be in huge trouble! Please stop!
What is that guy doing?!
Is he serious?!
You are annoying, too!
Translation, Yibis
Soundtracking, Halee
Editing, Sewil
Infoboxes, Sewil
Timing, Datenshi
Edit-checking, Galaxy 9000